Guide to the Student Christian Movement in New England Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Financial Material, 1929-1969; Series VIII
  - Danforth Foundation, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 595)
  - Earhart Foundation, 1938-1941 (Box 49, Folder 596)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955-1964 (Box 49, Folder 597)
  - Correspondence with individuals, 1935-1957 (Box 49, Folder 598)
  - Correspondence with individuals, 1960 (Box 49, Folder 599)
  - Correspondence with individuals, 1961-1967 (Box 49, Folder 600)
  - Correspondence re: Northern Student Movement, 1961-1967 (Box 50, Folder 601)
  - Minutes, reports, 1937-1942 (Box 50, Folder 602)
  - Minutes, reports, 1948-1956 (Box 50, Folder 603)
  - Minutes, reports, 1956-1967 (Box 50, Folder 604)
  - Solicitation records, 1929-1954 (Box 50, Folder 605)